<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Ziggy Cross</title>
    <link>https://ziggycross.dev/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Ziggy Cross</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://ziggycross.dev/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AI Safety via Debate</title>
      <link>https://ziggycross.dev/projects/aidebate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ziggycross.dev/projects/aidebate/</guid>
      <description>&lt;iframe&#xA;    width=&#34;600&#34;&#xA;    height=&#34;340&#34;&#xA;    src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/3bmo7Swxegw&#34;&#xA;    frameborder=&#34;0&#34;&#xA;    allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&#34;&#xA;    allowfullscreen&#xA;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://ai-debate.streamlit.app&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://img.shields.io/badge/Streamlit%20Cloud-grey?logo=Streamlit&amp;amp;logoColor=FF4B4B&amp;amp;labelColor=grey&amp;amp;color=FF4B4B&#34; alt=&#34;Streamlit Cloud&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kaggle.com/datasets/ziggycross/ai-debate&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://img.shields.io/badge/Kaggle-grey?logo=Kaggle&amp;amp;logoColor=white&amp;amp;labelColor=grey&amp;amp;color=20BEFF&#34; alt=&#34;Kaggle Dataset&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/ziggycross/ai-debate&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://img.shields.io/github/stars/ziggycross/ai-debate&#34; alt=&#34;GitHub Repo&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Does AI debate natually regress to specific &amp;lsquo;high-yield&amp;rsquo; topics? While reading AI Safety via Debate (Irving, G., Christiano, P. and Amodei, D., 2018), I jokingly asked if all debating LLMs were inherently marxist, as it was entirely possible a sufficiently long debate would always return to class struggle, or another similar &amp;lsquo;universal&amp;rsquo; problem.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Through this project I aimed to explore this idea further by creating a large dataset of AI debate transcripts and performing a semantic analysis using a Python library called BERTopic.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brainy</title>
      <link>https://ziggycross.dev/projects/brainy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ziggycross.dev/projects/brainy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Receiving support for mood disorders, anxiety, ADHD, and other mental health issues can be a daunting task. In BC, where 26% of residents don’t have a family doctor, access to treatment is additionally hindered by a lack of pre-existing medical records and lengthy gaps between appointments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Even after a first appointment with a general practitioner, BC patients face a median wait of 33.3 weeks before they begin receiving treatment. Given these limitations, the initial screening process - a short form, typically completed online - is a valuable tool for physicians who need to quickly identify and allocate appropriate treatments.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marshmallow Skirmish</title>
      <link>https://ziggycross.dev/projects/marshmallow/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ziggycross.dev/projects/marshmallow/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Marshmallow Skirmish was a charming and family-friendly first-person shooter game I developed in 2015. Along with my team, I took charge of Unity development and also handled designing and modeling the game environment. Collaborating with my classmates Austin Rule, who handled the concept art, and Brodie Anderson, who was responsible for the player and weapon models, we created an engaging game that captured the attention of both attendees and judges at the Young ICT Explorers competition.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2anonymity</title>
      <link>https://ziggycross.dev/projects/2anonymity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ziggycross.dev/projects/2anonymity/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Over one weekend, we developed a web tool for anonymizing data.&#xA;This was in response to one of the presented hackathon problems highlighting how anonymity is often a difficult-to-approach topic for researchers working with sensitive data.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Working with my team, I developed an algorithm for finding potentially identifying values and determining the best way to handle them.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Under the k-anonymity model, sensitive data can be handled in one of two ways:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
